Coffee's cold on the counter.
Fifty sets of boots by the door.
The TV's loud,
cam and stuff being scattered like a technicolor storm.
I'm just trying to find my keys.
You're in the center of the breeze,
handling it all with such ease.
And I'm just caught here in the view.
Watching all the things you do.
You're the calm inside the hurricane.
A whispering word that stops the rain.
It's an instinct I can't understand,
how you heal the world just with your hand.
It's a quiet strength,
a guiding light.
Oh,
the way you mother,
making everything right.
Right.
A nose bleed and a sudden cry,
you're there before the tear can dry.
A quiet word,
a healing kiss,
there's no problem you can't dismiss.
You're a judge,
a nurse,
a storyteller.
A fortress in a soft,
warm pillow.
You see the world right through their eyes without a hint of compromise.
And I'm just caught here in the view.
Watching all the things you do.
You're the calm inside the hurricane.
A whispering word that stops the rain.
It's an instinct I can't understand,
how you heal the world just with your hand.
It's a quiet strength,
a guiding light.
Oh,
the way you mother,
making everything right.
Oh,
right.
I try my best to play my part,
but you're the rhythm,
you're the heart.
You don't just build a house,
you build a home.
You plant the seeds and watch them grow with a patience I will never know.
Oh.
You're the calmest place I've ever known.
And I'm just caught here in the view.
Watching all the things you do.
You're the calm inside the hurricane.
A whispering word that stops the rain.
It's an instinct I can't understand,
how you heal the world just with your hand.
It's a quiet strength,
a guiding light.
Oh,
the way you mother,
making everything right.
The way you mother.
It's a quiet strength.
I'm just watching you.
Making everything right.
My amazing wife.
My amazing mother.